https://www.igl.net/moreinfo/privacy/

THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME
TO TIME. PLEASE CHECK THIS PAGE FOR UPDATES OR REQUEST THE LATEST COPY FROM LEGAL@THULIUMSOFTWARE.COM.
Welcome to CasesLadder.com (the .Site.) an interactive website specializing in Internet gaming ladders, leagues and tournaments (the .Services.). The Site is owned and operated by Case.s Ladder (the .Network.). Cases Ladder developed this privacy policy to demonstrate its firm commitment to protecting your privacy and personal information and to inform you on how this information is handled. This privacy policy applies only to transactions and activities you engage in, and data gathered, on the Site.
Please review this privacy policy
from time to time as it may be modified without notice. Each time you visit the Site or provide the Network with information, by doing so you are agreeing to the terms of this privacy policy at that time.
1. Collection of Information.
1.1 Survey Information.
The Network collects information from individuals when such individuals
voluntarily complete surveys, order forms, send an email through the
the Site's referral engine technology or submit information via online forms
which may or may not be accompanied by a pre-checked or non-pre-checked
checkbox indicating that such individuals consent to receiving marketing
communications from the Site or registration pages either online or offline, or by means of online or offline
surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (each, a
"Survey"). (As used herein, "online" means using the Internet,
including the websites and related technologies, and "offline" means
by methods other than online, including in person, via postal mail, telephones,
and other similar means.) In the Surveys, the Network or a third party may ask
individuals to provide various information which may include
their name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers, birth
date, gender, salary range, education level, marital status, occupation,
employment information, personal and online interests, and such other
information as may be requested from time to time (collectively, "Survey
Information"). Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and
individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to the
Network or any third party, but individuals may receive incentives from the
Network or a third party in exchange for providing Survey Information to the
Network.
1.2 Other Information.
Other occasions when the Network obtains information from individuals include
when such individuals (1) make a claim for a prize or seek to redeem an
incentive offered by the Network or a third party, (2) request assistance
through the Network's customer service department, and (3) voluntarily
subscribe to a Network service or newsletter (collectively, "Other
Information").
1.3 Cookies, Web beacons, and Other
Information Collected Using Technology.
(a) Case's Ladder uses "cookies" to enable you to sign in to the Site and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by the domain server that issued you the cookie. Case's Ladder uses cookies to store your preferences and enhance your online experience. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser to decline cookies.
If you choose to decline cookies, you may not have access to certain areas of the Site that depend on cookies. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. .
(b) Third Party Cookies.  The Network sends to your web browser many of the advertisements you see when you
use the Site. However, it also allow other companies, called
third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Site's web
pages. Because your web browser must request these advertising banners from the
ad network Web site, these companies can send their own cookies to your cookie
file, just as if you had requested a web page from the site. Please note that
if an advertiser asks the Network to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for
example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 13-24 who
have viewed sports content) and you respond to that ad, the advertiser or
ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are
trying to reach.  As always remember, the Network only authorize certain
third-party ad servers to employ anonymous cookies for ad delivery and
anonymous targeting.  The third-party ad
servers do not collect, nor does the Network give them access, to any personally
identifying information about you. If you want to prevent a third-party ad server from sending and reading cookies on your computer, you must visit each ad network.s web site individual and opt out (if they offer this capability.)
(c) Web beacons. Web beacons are graphic images, often transparent
and no larger than 1 pixel x 1 pixel, that are placed on a Web site or in an
e-mail. Web beacons are used to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the
Web site or opening the e-mail. When the HTML code for the Web beacon points to
a site to retrieve the image, it simultaneously can pass along information such
as the IP address of the computer that retrieved the image, the time the Web
beacon was viewed and for how long, the type of browser that retrieved the
image and previously set cookie values. The Network, or third parties acting on
the its behalf, may utilize Web beacons on Web pages or in email for any
legally permissible purpose.
(d) General Behavior Tracking. The Network may track online behaviors
("Behaviors") through its own technologies, including its desktop
software products, in order to increase the effectiveness of the advertisements
it delivers. Examples of such behaviors may include advertisement responses,
websites that individuals visit, and products that individuals purchase. Individuals
can prevent the tracking of Behaviors by globally unsubscribing from the
Network's marketing materials. The Network
reserves the right to use such technologies for any purpose permitted by law.
(e) Information Automatically
Collected. For site
maintenance, optimization, security and other legally permissible purposes, the
Network's servers (or third party servers) may collect certain information
about website visitors automatically. Such information may include such visitors'
IP address, browser type, date, time and duration of visit and particular pages
viewed, and such other information as is permitted by law.
(f) New Technology. The use of technology on the Internet is rapidly
evolving, as is the Network's use of new technology. As previously stated,
Network reserves the right to change this policy at any time without any
additional notice to the user. As a result, the Network strongly encourages
individuals to revisit this privacy policy from time to time for any updates
regarding its use of technology. Use of any Network website constitutes
acknowledgement and acceptance of the Network's Privacy Policy and the
Network's right to modify such Privacy Policy without additional notice.
1.4 Outside Information. The Network may receive information about
individuals from a third party or from other sources of information outside of
the Network including information located in public databases ("Outside
Information").
1.5 Individual Information. As used herein, "Individual Information"
means Survey Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and
Outside Information, and any other information the Network gathers or receives
about individuals.
1.6 No Information Collected from
Children. The Network will
never knowingly or intentionally collect any personal information about
children under the age of 13. If the Network obtains actual knowledge that it
has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that
information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not
knowingly or intentionally collect such information, to the best of the
Network's knowledge and belief, the Network has no such information to use or
to disclose to a third party. The Network has designed this policy in order to
comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.
1.7 Credit Card Information. The Network may in certain cases collect credit card
numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card
("Credit Card Information") when an individual places an order from
Network. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to the Network, such
information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. The
Network will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and
completing the purchase transaction, and the Credit Card Information will be
disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete the purchase
transaction.
2. Use of Individual Information.
2.1 Discretion to Use Information.
THE NETWORK MAY USE INDIVIDUAL
INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN THE NETWORK'S SOLE
DISCRETION. The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how
the Network currently uses Individual Information, but the Network may change
or broaden its use at any time as permitted by law. As noted below, the Network
may update this policy from time to time. The Network may use Individual
Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email
advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, and online banner
advertising, among other uses.
2.2 Email.
The Network uses Individual Information to provide promotional offers by email
to individuals who have permitted use of their email address for this purpose.
The Network may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email
recipients wish to end their email subscription, they need to follow the
instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe.
2.3 Targeted Advertising.
The Network uses Individual Information to target advertising to individuals.
When individuals use the Internet, the Network uses such persons' Individual
Information to show advertising for products and services in which those users
have expressed an interest, whether directly or indirectly.
2.4 Direct Mail and Telemarketing.
The Network may use Individual Information to advertise or provide promotional
offers, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or
telemarketing using telephones, as permitted by law.
2.6 Storage of Individual
Information.
The Network stores Individual Information in a database on Network computers.
Network computers have security measures (such as firewalls) in place to
reasonably protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information
under the Network's control. Notwithstanding such measures, the Network cannot
guarantee that its security measures will prevent Network computers from being
illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.
2.7 Rights of Third Party Affiliates.
Network may extend any of its rights under this Agreement to third parties
performing services on its behalf.
3. Dissemination of Individual
Information.
3.1 Sale to Third Parties.
The Network may sell or transfer Individual Information to third parties in
connection with any merger, acquisition, reorganization, change in capital
structure, sale of all or substantially all of the assets of any Network
division or website, or any activity specified in Section 3.2, 3.3, or 3.4
below.
3.2 Order Fulfillment.
The Network will transfer Individual Information to third parties as necessary
to provide a product or service that an individual orders from such third party
while using one of the Network's websites or when responding to offers provided
by the Network.
3.3 Legal Process.
The Network may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, search
warrants, court orders, or other legal process.
3.4 Summary Data.
The Network may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary
or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.
4. Privacy Practices of Third
Parties.
4.1 Advertiser cookies and web
beacons.
Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (collectively,
"Advertisers") who place advertisements on the Network's websites and
on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other
technology to collect information about individuals. The Network does not
control Advertisers' use of such technology and the Network has no
responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about
individuals.
4.2 Links.
The Network's websites and email messages may contain hypertext links to the
websites of one or more third parties. The Network is not responsible for the
privacy practices or the content of such other websites.
4.3 Affiliated Companies.
The Network may disclose, transfer and sell Individual Information to an entity
which becomes affiliated with Network through formation, merger or acquisition,
in the Network's discretion.
5. Unsubscribe from Case's Ladder lists.
The Network maintains multiple newsletter
and email marketing lists. To unsubscribe from one or more of such lists, click
the link included in the footer of any message delivered by the Network and
follow the instructions provided.
6. More Information.
If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at legal@thuliumsoftware.com. THE NETWORK RESERVES THE RIGHT TO UPDATE THIS POLICY
FROM TIME TO TIME, SO YOU SHOULD REVIEW THIS WEB PAGE PERIODICALLY.
Copyright 1996 - 2020 Case's Ladder, Inc. All Rights Reserved. Copyright Policy.
www.casesladder.com | Premium Memberships | Privacy Policy
